{
    "subject": "resource/Sanaya_Irani",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Indian_soap_opera_actresses",
    "human_readable": "Sanaya Irani's subject is Category:Indian soap opera actresses.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9637786746025085,
            "question": "Is Sanaya Irani associated with Indian soap operas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.856021523475647,
            "question": "What type of actress is Sanaya Irani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6766189336776733,
            "question": "In which category does Sanaya Irani fall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6673951148986816,
            "question": "Can you name any soap operas featuring Sanaya Irani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6647481322288513,
            "question": "What kind of roles has Sanaya Irani played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.600910484790802,
            "question": "What is Sanaya Irani's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.594810426235199,
            "question": "Is Sanaya Irani recognized for her acting skills?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5861213207244873,
            "question": "What is Sanaya Irani known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4775133728981018,
            "question": "To which country does Sanaya Irani belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3474437892436981,
            "question": "Does Sanaya Irani work in the entertainment industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sanaya Irani's subject is Category:Indian soap opera actresses.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4632_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Sanaya Irani belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4632_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Sanaya Irani known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4632_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Sanaya Irani recognized for her acting skills?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4632_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4632_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4632_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4632_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4632_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4632_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4632_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4632_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4632_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4632_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4632_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Sanaya Irani being an Indian actress and television actress, which supports the categorization of her as a Category:Indian soap opera actress."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Sanaya Irani's subject is listed as Category:Fiction television actresses.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}